

INDUSTRIAL DESIGNER · WEB DEVELOPER

Monterrey, Nuevo León, México

□ (+52) 81 16 95 16 02 | Image: miguelalejandrodelamoraarocha@gmail.com | Image: miguel-de-la-mora-arocha

Summary_

I am Miguel De La Mora, Industrial Design graduate with a specialized focus on web development and a strong background in UX UI design. My academic journey has culminated in a comprehensive understanding of design principles and their seamless integration into web-based applications.

Work Experience

Cantú Herrera Asesores

Monterrey, Nuevo León

ACCOUNTING ASSISTANT

Jun. 2019 - Feb. 2024

Perform accounting for specific clients, monthly tax declarations, modifications to tax activities, issuing electronic invoices, among other tasks.
 Tools: Excel, Office.

Global Pear Monterrey, Nuevo León

WEB DESIGNER

Mar. 2024 - Current

• Designing websites for various clients, application of SEO and marketing strategies and development of new ticketing website.

Honors & Awards

2022 **Academic Merit**, 8th Semester. Universidad Autónoma de Nuevo León

Monterrey, México

Skills

Design Tools, Figma, InDesign, Miro, AdobeXD, Illustrator, Photoshop

Programming Languages, Html, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript

Programming Tools, Git, Github, WordPress, React.js, Vite.js, Tailwind CSS

Languages, Spanish, English, Italian

Soft Skills, Problem Solving and critical thinking, Adaptability, Teamwork, Willingness to learn, Time

Management

Courses_

2023 Google UX Design Certificate, Coursera

Monterrey, México

023 Front-End Programa Orcale Next-Education, Alura LATAM

Monterrey, México

Education

UANL(Universidad Autónoma de Nuevo León)

Monterrey, Nuevo León, México

Jan. 2019 - Dec. 2023

B.S. IN INDUSTRIAL DESIGN

UXUI Design Path

• Web Developer

Projects _____

Web Design

Monterrey, Nuevo León

GLOBAL PEAR

Mar. 2024 - Current

- Website Helped in the website design team to build a website for ISGO Tech, Capstone Dufrane, Grupo Asesores, Counselors International and Global Pear implementing visually appealing elements, responsive design, Search Engine Optimization (SEO) and maintenance.
- Ticketing Website Design for ticketing website. Adding events, creating seating maps and maintenance.

Web Design Monterrey, Nuevo León

Freelance Sep. 2023 - Current

- Movie Ticketing App-Research, methodologies, tools for knowing the user and background. Design and prototype in Figma.
- The website for Rosa Carmin is being redesigned, following the 'Mobile first' methodology.
- To Do List App Website App made with HTML, CSS and JavaScript, where the user can add tasks and are saved in the local storage.
- Lopez + Segura Architecture Webpage: Currently making a website for an architecture office using Figma, HTML, CSS and Javascript.
- E-Commerce Website: Website built with React + Vite, using an API of products. Logic implemented for added products, past orders, filtering products by category, etc.

Packaging DesignMonterrey, Nuevo LeónUANLAug. 2023 - Dec. 2023

• Design of branding and packaging for Cayetana Bakery.